fanzila.com 2012-11-18

# Fanzila - Privacy Policy

## Online Privacy Policy

Last updated: September, 2011

This Privacy Policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") describes the policies and practices of **Dex Technologies Ltd.** (" **we** ," " **us** ," or " **Fanzila** ") with respect to all information collected or used by us in connection with this Website at www.fanzila.com (" **Website** ") as well as the Fanzila Service, a service offered via the Website which enables the establishment, management and maintenance of a community site with Facebook (" **Fanzila Service** "; the Website and the Fanzila Services shall hereinafter be referred to collectively as the " **Service** "). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to enable you to understand how we collect and use information relating to you. Please review carefully this Privacy Policy before making any use of the Service. Each use of the Service by you constitutes your consent to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Please be advised that your use of Facebook in general and your relationship with Facebook are subject to Facebook’s own privacy policy and Facebook’s other terms and policies, which we strongly recommend that you review before you start using the Service. We do not control and are not responsible for Facebook’s processing of your information. 

BY REGISTERING WITH US, ALLOWING US TO ACCESS YOUR FACEBOOK INFORMATION AND/OR MAKING USE OF THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE US OR PERMIT US TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, AND DO NOT USE THE SERVICE.

### Personally Identifiable Information we Collect

The Service is operated by a third party service provider on our behalf, and your personal information will be collected for us by such third party service provider.

In order to facilitate the Fanzila Service, we may collect personal information and content that was provided by you or other users to Facebook or was associated by Facebook with a particular user ("Facebook Information"). When you use the Service, we may collect any Facebook Information you have made visible to "Everyone" on Facebook as well as the information Facebook designates as your publicly available information. This includes: name, profile picture, gender, current city and networks. When using the Service, you will also be asked to grant us access to additional Facebook Information that you are allowed to share under Facebook’s policies. Currently, we ask that you share all information that you are allowed to share under Facebook policies. This information includes: 

  * your contact information, including your email address, phone number and mailing address
  * items you have "liked" and your "like" associations
  * your profile information, including your date of birth, gender, location, employment history and education history

Even if you have not explicitly allowed us access to any of your Facebook Information, we may collect information about you when your friends on Facebook allow access to and use the Service, subject to your Facebook settings. We may also send you emails and post on your Facebook Wall in connection with your use of the Service. 

In addition to the Facebook Information, when you create an account with us through our Website, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself such as your name, user name, email address, password, and date of birth (such information shall be referred to as " **User Information** "). Your User Information will be stored in our database by our third party service provider and will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
You are not required to provide us with your User Information in order to view certain portions of the Website and the Service, however, please be advised that if you decide not to provide certain User Information or permit access to your Facebook Information you might not be able to use certain features of the Service.

### How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information

The personally identifiable information you provide to us directly or through permission to access your Facebook Information may be used for a variety of purposes, such as to register with, log-in, and use the Service, and interact with other users of the Service. Your personally identifiable information may also allow us to communicate with you about administrative issues, improve the contents provided through the Service and communicate with you about promotions, special offers and new features. We may also use your personally identifiable information for internal analytical purposes intended to improve the services we provide. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to advertisers or spammers. 

### How We Share Your Personally Identifiable Information

We may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties (a) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process (including any court order) or governmental request, (b) to perform certain administrative functions consistent with our Privacy Policy on our behalf, including in connection with customer support, web hosting and design services, fulfillment services (such as, mailing services), and data analysis, (c) to protect the safety of our employees and our property, and (d) in connection with enforcement of this Privacy Policy. We may also share with some of our business partners (such as, data collection companies) general information related to your use of the Service without disclosing your identity in order to improve the Service and your user experience. When our third party service providers collect and/or have access to any information other than non-personal anonymous data, we require that they use such data consistently with our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of personal information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by Fanzila. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose without your specific consent.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information we Collect and How we Use it

When you use the Service we may also collect from you information which is not personally identifiable by use of "cookie" technology, web beacons, and log file information for purposes such as: (a) collect website users' usage data to enable easy access to the Service and otherwise improve the Service; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of the Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries and submissions to the Service. A "cookie" is a small data file that is transferred to your device's hard disk. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You should change your browser settings if you do not wish to accept cookies from us on your device.

### Public Information Including User Generated Content, Online Forums, Blogs and Profiles

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content to our Service through our discussion boards (such as, Facebook "Wall" and "Links" features), user "profiles" for public view or in similar forums on our Service. Information that you disclose and content you submit (such as videos, images or photos) in any of these forums becomes public information, and therefore, you should not have any expectation of privacy or confidentiality in such areas in connection with any content you submit. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information and other content you submit in the course of these public activities can be read, collected, copied and/or used by other users of these discussion boards without your consent, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information and content you choose to submit in these discussion boards or elsewhere in our Service.  
Without derogating from the foregoing, we further wish you to be advised that when you choose to join a certain blog forum or any other community established by a user of the Service you acknowledge and agree that your personally identifiable information, including your Facebook Information will be accessible to the community manager as well as to Fanzila and may be used in connection with utilization of the Service and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### How You Can Protect Your Privacy

When you submit or make available your personally identifiable information and other personal information through the Service, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of such information pursuant to this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish that we collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information and do not allow us access to your Facebook account information. If you do not wish other users of our Service to have access to information and content you submit to our Service, please do not submit such information or content.  
Subject to applicable law we provide you with access to the User Information we have retained about you and the ability to review, correct, update, block or delete the information where it is inaccurate (except for Facebook Information which is not accessible via the Service). Subject to applicable law, we may limit or deny access to your User Information where providing such access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances. Please submit your request to the address specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below. 

### Opt-Out Options and Unsubscribing

Fanzila may send you from time to time, through the Facebook application, email communications with news and updates about the Service or other products as well as other marketing communications and promotional offers. If you do not wish to receive from us such marketing communications, you can opt-out, at any time, by following the procedures set forth in the communications sent to you. Please be sure to include your full name and email address and indicate what type of marketing communications you do not wish to receive any longer. We will take appropriate steps to fulfill your request, however, it may take a few days or longer to process your request during which you may still receive marketing communications from us. Fanzila reserves the right to send you notices about your account, even if you opt-out of all email notifications.  
If you decide to terminate your account with us, you may do so by removing the application through Facebook or by sending us an email to support@fanzila.com specifying your request and providing us with your name and email address. If you terminate your account, your profile will be removed from the Service, however, deletion may not be immediate and Fanzila may continue keeping your personal information in its records for audits and other administrative purposes. If you have granted us access to your Facebook account information you can request deletion of your Facebook information by dissociating the Fanzila application from your Facebook account via Facebook’s Application Settings page. 

### Links

Our Service may contain links to third parties' web sites (including the Facebook website). The fact that we link to a site is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. While we attempt to provide links to sites that value your privacy, we cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policies of such sites. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of such third parties' sites linked or provided through our Service prior to any use of such sites.

### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to refer a friend to the Service, we will ask you to provide your friend's email address. This information will be used only to send a one-time message to your friend inviting him or her to register with the Service.

### Business Transfers

In the conduct of our business, we may sell certain of our assets. Information collected from users of the Service, including personal information, could be transferred as part of such transaction. By submitting your personal information through the Service or granting access to your Facebook account information, you agree that your information may be transferred to third parties under such or similar circumstances.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Fanzila may occasionally revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in its Service and other practices. Therefore, you should review this Privacy Policy prior to each use of the Service, so you could be informed of any changes in our privacy practices. At all times, the most current version of our privacy policy will govern and supersede any other versions of our privacy policy. You can determine when the Privacy Policy was last modified by checking the "Last updated" legend at the top of the Privacy Policy. If the policies described in our Privacy Policy change in any material respect, we will notify you by posting the revised policy on our Service, by email, or by other means that we may choose and as required by applicable law. We may apply changes to information previously collected by us, to the extent permitted by law. If you do not agree to be bound by the terms of the new or modified Privacy Policy, you agree to immediately notify us that your account with the Service should be terminated and that your personal information should be deleted. Your continued use of the Service after such changes become effective constitutes your acceptance of any such changes.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by email at support@fanzila.com.

### General

This Privacy Policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided to you about our privacy practices associated with the Service. The examples contained in this Privacy Policy are for illustrations purpose only and are not intended to be exhaustive.
